[Applause]
Wow.
>> Oh, it's a hot night in Philadelphia.
>> Yeah.
What's up?
Put your [\h__\h]
>> back to Australia. James M. You guys are
thrilled about America.
[Applause]
>> I like that you can abbreviate it into
one America. Just one sound,
which I found out is this is America.
There it's a full set cuz it sounds like
it's just short for America, but it's
short for this is America,
which you shout
a lot. I mean that you go to the Rose
Bowl and there's a fighter jet going
overhead and people go this is America
America. It's like yes no one else is
getting the military involved in
collegiate sport.
That is just you guys.
But they say that everywhere like you go
to England and they go
for them it's a question. It's a sad
question
cuz I go I go I love England. They go
English [\h__\h] I [\h__\h] hate England.
It's all Muslims and crime.
This is England. I can't believe I'm
glad the queen is dead.
So she don't have to live. I say what
they
say. We say it in Australia. We say this
is Australian.
We say it at Vietnamese people on the
bus. We put this Australian. You better
speak Australian if you're Australian.
And that's not racist because it's our
culture.
Taking it away from us would be the
racist.
Anyway,
a lot of people say it. The Chinese say
it. The Chinese love saying this is
China. Yep. They sadly they keep saying
it in places that are not China.
They say it in Hong Kong. They say it in
Tibet. They say it in parts of the sea.
That joke was originally about Israel,
but my manager asked me to make it about
China for some reason.
>> I don't know why. My manager, my
accountant, my lawyer, my agent,
everybody said, "I think that joke is a
lot funnier if it's about China."
I I'm just I'm trying to fit in. All
right.
There are You guys have to I'm not
allowed to talk about Israel.
You guys have a first amendment. And
that's great. I'm here on a visa. I
don't have one.
And that's one of two things I'm not
allowed to talk about. I also don't have
a second amendment right. I'm not
allowed to own a gun that the government
knows about, but I am in Texas and it's
so easy. Anyway,
I do have a 13th amendment.
I'm not allowed to own a slave, but the
first two amendments
No first amendment. There's there's
generally two things I'm not allowed to
talk about. One of them is criticizing
Marco Rubio passed a thing that if you
criticize Israel, you can lose your
visa. I'm allowed to criticize America
all I want. I am not. If I criticize
Israel, I'm genuinely. But I wouldn't
want to.
What is there to
complain about
at all? genuinely
too peaceful. That's all I would say. I
listen I I love I That's the camera. I
love Israel. I love it. I'm a big fan.
Uh
sir, what is the month? What is the
month that comes after June?
>> July. I would never say that,
>> you know. I prefer to call that month
Jew tell the truth. I think that's a
better name for that month.
I am sick of all the anti-Israel
propaganda that I'm seeing. I saw a
Facebook post where someone said Israel
has killed or injured 50,000 children in
Gaza.
That's not fair.
I've injured 12 children, I would say,
in my life. something like 12 children
as a child or through negligence as a
father. I'd say I've injured
there have been 12 child related
injuries. I've killed zero children. But
if you came out with a thing that said
James McCann has killed or injured 12
children. While accurate, that would
make me seem worse.
So there'll be no more discussion of
Israel.
No,
[Music]
I am allowed to criticize America, but I
don't want to cuz I love it here so
much. It's It's been so good to me. I've
even got a favorite school shooting. And
uh
I don't know about you guys. I don't
know if you guys have a favorite school
shooting
if you're just waiting to see what the
new year brings. I don't uh
Well, I'll tell you about my favorite
school shooting. It was a girl who did
it, which is rare.
>> All right, the vibe is shifted.
I'll play a song. I'll play a song while
I describe my favorite.
All right.
Can you hear? So, this girl goes to
school with a I think it's a revolver.
She gets six shots. She unloads them
into her teacher and her classmates.
[Music]
She missed everybody. That's my favorite
bit about it. She missed everybody. She
hit the walls. She hit a desk. I don't
know if she heard school shooting and
she thought, "I'm going to go and shoot
the school." But
worst thing that happened was a splinter
came off a table and hit a teacher in
the hand. I swear.
Isn't that great?
She didn't even save a bullet for
herself.
That's school shooter 101. She went bang
bang bang bang bang bang click click.
I want to be the policeman going in to
get her after kick down the door. Hey,
>> you got to apologize to these people.
You got
I can't remember if that really happened
or if it's a dream that I had.
Second thing I'm not meant to talk about
is black people. I uh I've noticed that
that doesn't work out for the whites
ever. There's never like a news story on
CNN where it's like a white guy has
spoken on black America and he's really
hit the nail on the head. We're all
thrilled with what he said and genuinely
that could tarnish my visa. These are
the only two things that I think could
hurt my
You would think there would be more, but
I I think genuinely I've got it down to
those two. If you I mean any racial hate
gets me out. Uh so we'll be a bit
careful. The uh like when you're trying
to get into America, there's a list of
crimes that you can't have committed if
you want to come into America with a
visa. And it's like murder and you go,
that's fine. You know, I haven't done
that. But they'll go like, you know, if
you do a murder, you'll never get an
office job in America. You got to walk
across that border like everybody else.
But then there's a secondary list of
crimes.
And they're crimes that you can have
committed unless you've done them as a
hate crime somehow. So an assault, fine,
hate crime, assault, very bad. And some
of that, some of that's all right. But
then I'm looking at it going, "How do I
do a racially motivated drink driving?
[Applause]
What steps do I actually have to take to
get that done? I got to go to a 7-Eleven
and give me give me nine fireballs and
directions to West Philadelphia, please.
I can see no way to do it.
I have no interest in talking about the
state of Israel or African-Ameans,
but the fact that I'm not allowed to do
it really makes me want to. And when I
was young, that was like a that felt
like a good attribute. They can't tell
me what to say. I'm going to say
whatever I want to say. And as I get
older, it's just a big liability that
stops people hanging out with me in
groups.
I was I was backstage and Alpuccino's
baby mama was there for some reason. The
mother of Alpuccino's child, it's a
circle, me and some friends, and the
mother of Alpuccino's she's young and
he's Aluccino. He's a very old man. And
someone says, "This is Alpuccino's the
mother of his child." And another friend
grabbed me by the arm and walked me
away.
I said, "I didn't do anything wrong." He
said, "I think you were going to. I'm
not sure, but it felt like you were
going to ask some inappropriate
questions." And I was going to ask if
the baby seemed unusually wise, but uh
so I will not talk about black people
and I will not talk about Israel.
All right. Here's a big problem with
Israel, as far as I can. You've got to
kill a lot of innocent people to build a
country.
>> I'm sorry. Have you forgotten?
That's the only way to do it. You've A
lot of innocent people have to die. If
you're going You guys did it. You never
talk about it because you did a lot of
slavery afterwards and you really want
to focus on the slavery. I get it.
It's you can focus on one thing at a
time and that's bigger for you. I get
it. Canada didn't do the slavery. They
can't stop going on about stealing the
land. But
you guys did the slavery. You got to
work through that. It's like you've gone
to a house party and [\h__\h] your pants and
then punched somebody in the throat, you
know, and afterwards everybody goes,
"Oh, he punched that guy in the throat.
That's terrible." But it's going to take
a while before people start going, "I
think he [\h__\h] his pants." Got to work
backwards through it.
[Applause]
People have to.
Those were the rules
for all of human history. The rules were
we kill you, we take it. Goodbye. Don't
the ones who are left, if you complain,
we're going to kill you, too.
You guys messed that up for everybody. I
can criticize America. You guys are the
real problem here. After World War II,
you had the bomb. No one else had the
bomb. You said, "Time out. These lines
on the map are beautiful. We're going to
keep them exactly as they are." All
right. cuz you had the best lines. You
didn't want to [\h__\h] with your lines at
all. You You're not going to fill up
Wyoming with suburbs for a thousand
years. You were very happy to say,
"Whoa, time out. These are the lines.
Time back in. Israel exists. Time out
again." All right. Now that we've made
that one correction, this new rule about
where the lines are. That has never been
the case ever at any point in all of
humanity.
All right. Black people. Now the no I I
do want to get to the
you you deserve credit for this as a
country is that like for four years
you've had the nuclear bomb and you
didn't do anything with other than the
first couple of times you okay you got
it and you used it twice and then you
said no one's ever using these again.
People said didn't you guys just use
them? You're like, "Yeah, we were
excited to get them, but now that we're
more of a do as I say, not as I explode
type of nation. Now that I've got them,
we're just going to have peace
everywhere." More or less. Basically,
peace. That's incredible. You were the
only nuclear power. No one could [\h__\h]
with you. And that's what you went with.
No one else would have done that. Give
yourselves a pat on the back for that.
If I was the prime minister of Australia
and we got the nuke, I would have been
going crazy. I would I would have been
there with a megaphone going, "Hey,
Spain,
put hats on the dogs. Spain, I want
photos.
I want every dog to have a hat in
Spain." All right, Thailand, send over a
million hot women. They have to be
women. They have to be real women. Don't
try and trick us. Example
number three. Third thing. Do you know
what I'm saying?
[Applause]
All right. Now,
I'm a big fan of black people. I don't
know how many I've managed to bring out
to my show. This is a very fractured
media landscape,
but I like it. It's new to me. I'm not
from a country that has black people.
That's entirely
We have Aboriginal people and we have
African people, but we have no soul
power. Do you understand?
>> I'm from an all-white country. If you're
on a flight in Australia and there's a
bumpy landing, everybody's silent.
People that say nothing and they got
their hands crossed and they're anxious
and they're scared and then you just
carry that nervous tension around with
you for like a week.
In America, if there is a bumpy landing,
there will be a black guy on the flight
and he's going to go, "Oh." And you know
what? Genuinely, thank you for saying
that out loud. You've helped us all work
through the tension together. I believe
that's called keeping it real. And I'm a
big fan of it.
[Applause]
I had my first conversation with a black
woman in February last year.
I had met a couple of black guys before
because not everyone's good enough to
play in the NBA. And we send our scouts
out to your colleges and we say, "Did
you want to come and dunk on some honks
for a year?" And uh every team in
Australia is allowed to have one
American.
It's always a black guy. Every time it's
We've never once got a gangly boy from
Utah to come out. It's never an Eastern
European guy. It's always a black guy.
And I get to meet my first first real
conversation with a black lady. It was I
was in West Virginia at a Taco Bell.
I didn't know what parts of the country
were important to visit first.
It's not there.
Yeah, it's almost heaven, West Virginia.
Almost doing a lot of the heavy lifting
in that.
It's purgatory.
Everybody, I was I went to the I was
buying my Doritos tacos so I could feel
a little less suicidal.
You know how it is. And I came around to
the intercom and everybody was like
eight people gathered around the
intercom laughing at my accent. I don't
think anyone from outside of this
country had ever been to this West
Virginia Taco Bell. I don't know what
would bring them there. Anyway, I don't
know what I It's a long story. I got to
the first window. There was a lady
there. She said, "Where are you from?" I
said, "I'm from Australia." And then to
be cheeky, I said, "Are you from
Australia?"
And she said, "I'm black.
Do they treat black people nicely in
Australia?" And I said, "No." And I
drove on to the next window. I was not
ready to have a full civics
conversation.
You tap and you go.
I just sat at the next window feeling
very sad and embarrassed.
And then I was more embarrassed when she
appeared at the second window, which was
not her job. She had left. She had taken
the headset off, walked the full length
of the Taco Bell, leaned across
somebody, and said, "You really got a
problem with black people in Australia,
and I I said, "Listen, I I love black
people, I think. Uh, this is about
number four that I've ever my entire
life, but I'm a big fan."
I was trying to say my country has a
problem. And she said, "Oh, well, that's
what's up." and she gave me a fist bump
and it was the happiest day of my whole
life. I've honestly never been so
thrilled. I've joined the team. I'm an
ally.
I started smoking menthol cigarettes. I
took it.
Bill Cosby didn't do it.
He was a good man brought down by some
people I'm unable to speak about right
now.
We love Bill.
Well, the love for Bill goes hard out
here in Philadelphia to this day.
Does women's happiness was a small price
to pay.
>> No, he definitely did. The uh
I am genuinely a big Kanye fan though.
I'm I really
>> Not the music, just the politics. I love
Kanye. And by the way, by the way, not
the anti-semitism. The anti-semitism I
disapprove of entirely. the
anti-abortion stuff 100% of the way with
Kanye. Listen, we don't have to talk
about that either. I shouldn't talk
about that either. There's a couple more
things I shouldn't talk anyway. We'll
get to that potentially in the
>> I love Kanye. I'm such a I'm a big Kanye
defender. When he came out the first
time and said he loved Hitler, I was
defending him that day. I said he only
said that because he's a Christian and
he loves everybody, even Hitler. And
that's a good Christian.
That's what we're all called to do as
Christian. Loving each other here this
evening. That is entry levelvel
Christianity. Kanye loving Hitler.
That's advanced.
He's brought himself to love even
Hitler.
This is saintly behavior.
And then Kanye came out shortly after
that and said he also really liked
Hitler. And I I thought,
"No,
that's ever so much worse.
Kanye likes Hitler." I don't know if
Hitler would like Kanye. I've been uh
I suspect he would not. But I could be
right. I mean, I could be. Maybe Hitler
would love Kanye. Hitler would Hitler
like, "Wow, you're so cool. I love you.
I love the jungle music and the I love
the future shoes,
which I'm a big fan of your ex-wife with
the big fat ass.
You know, that's a gas chamber we can
all get behind. I do believe
I could that could go on for too long.
We better pull out of that immediately.
[Applause]
>> I'll tell you about my favorite ever
Kanye West lyric.
Favorite Kanye lyric of all time is when
I go raw, I like to leave it in.
You may know a thing or two about the
When I go raw, I like to leave it in. We
do. We all know what that means.
>> No condom and you ejaculate in the
[\h__\h]
>> It's the only way to do it. That's what
I It sounds dirty. It's not. That's one
of the few rap lyrics you could play to
the Pope, you know? and he could hear
that and he'd go, "Yeah,
that's how we've been telling people to
do it for a long time."
I'm so glad a fellow Chicago Southsider
is spreading the good word
about going raw and leaving it in.
It's the only way to do it. It's the
It's the only.
If you got a friend who's depressed, you
say, "Have you tried going raw and
leaving it in because I think you'll be
thrilled by the
who who loves condoms.
It's what I thought.
I'm pulling out."
Who pulls out?
It's one of the worst reaction times
I've ever heard.
That is not going to be an effective
method of contracepting for you.
>> Pulling out is gross and evil and it
makes sex bad and lame.
[Applause]
I'm not allowed to give this speech at
middle schools anymore. So, I've had to
become a comedian. I really am a big
anti-pull out guy. It ruins the sex.
Yeah, cuz you know it's like going to a
party and leaving your hat on the whole
time and you cope and you're always
getting ready to leave. You never really
settle in.
Do you know what I'm saying? Sexual
congress is about you're meant to be
getting closer to one another and closer
until you get to the moment of ultimate
closeness at which point you have to go
get the [\h__\h] away from me.
It's not about pulling out here. It's
about pulling out here.
It's one of the things I like about
America. It's a very go raw, leave it in
country.
You don't call it that. You call it land
of the free and home of the brave.
Did you think about it? There's nothing
more free than going raw.
And there's nothing braver than leaving
it in. I mean, that
All
right, that's really all I wanted to
record. That'll be about a half hour.
[Music]
[Applause]